poolcorp.com 2018-11-27

# Pool Corporation | POOLCORP - Privacy Policy | POOLCORP.com

### Privacy Policy

At Pool Corporation, we respect our website guests and understand that you are concerned about privacy. We have therefore posted this Privacy Policy to let you know what kind of personal information we collect, how it is handled, and with whom it may be shared.

This Policy does not cover any interaction you may have with us by telephone, postal mail, or other offline communications. It applies only to the www.poolcorp.com website and other related websites that we have linked to this Privacy Policy (collectively “Websites”). Other websites operated by Pool Corporation, our subsidiaries or affiliates, or other third parties, may be governed by separate privacy policies, and we recommend that you review the privacy policies referenced on those websites.

These Websites are intended for users in the United States and are not intended for users in other locations. Users accessing these Websites from other locations do so on their own initiative and are responsible for compliance with local laws. 

Our Websites do not target and are not intended to attract children under the age of 13. We do not knowingly collect any personal information from children, and therefore we do not knowingly distribute such information to third parties.

**By visiting our Websites, you consent to our use of the information we collect from you according to this Privacy Policy, including our release of information to third parties as described below.**

### I. Information That We Collect

#### Personal Information

We collect various types of "personal information" depending on how you use our Websites. For example, when you register as a customer on our Websites, we collect your name, email address, mailing and shipping addresses, telephone numbers, and credit card information, so that we can process orders you submit through our Websites. When you begin or complete the job application process on our Websites, we collect your name, address, phone number, and other information, so that we can process your application.

You will always know when we are collecting personal information because we only collect personal information when you voluntarily submit it to us. If you do choose to give us personal information through our Websites, we will collect and retain that information, and you consent to the transfer and storage of that information on our servers. If you choose not to give us personal information, we may not be able to provide you with any services you may request or require.

#### Non-Personal Information

When you use our Websites, we may also collect "non-personal information," which is information that, by itself, cannot be used to identify or contact you, such as demographic information (such as your age, gender, income, education, profession, zip code, etc.) or technical information (such as your IP address, the type of browser you are using, and the websites you visit immediately before and immediately after you visit our Websites). Non-personal information may also include information that you provide us through your use of our Websites, such as the terms you enter into the search functions of our Websites.

#### Cookies

When you visit or interact with our Websites, we (or our third-party providers) may use "cookies" or other similar technologies to personalize and enhance your experience. A “cookie” is a small piece of information sent to a visitor’s computer or other Internet-connected devices to uniquely identify the visitor’s browser or to store information or settings in the browser. Our Websites use both session cookies and persistent cookies.

Session cookies enable you to move from page to page and to use features on our Websites while your browser remains open. For example, session cookies allow you to add products to your shopping cart and carry the contents of your cart to checkout.

Persistent cookies last from visit to visit. For example, persistent cookies may be used to recognize you as a previous user to provide a more personalized experience. They are stored in your computer, device, or browser until you choose to delete them.

The majority of web browsers accept cookies and similar files, but you can usually change the browser settings to prevent this. However, if you do so, some functionality of our Websites may be lost. Please visit [www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/) for more information about cookies and how to disable them.

#### Do Not Track

Our Websites currently do not respond to Do Not Track signals in browsers. Third parties that have content embedded on our website (such as buttons, widgets, and other embedded features or content) may set cookies on your browser or obtain information about the fact that you visited our websites from a certain IP address. Our third-party providers may also collect personal information as described in this Policy, and we encourage you to review the privacy policies of those third parties.

### II. How We Use the Information We Collect

We use the non-personal information we collect to analyze how our Websites are being used, and to improve the content of our Websites, online product offerings, and marketing and promotional efforts.

If you choose to provide personal information to us, we may use your personal information in a number of ways, including to provide you with the services you have requested, to process orders or respond to inquiries, to administer contests and surveys, and to communicate offers and other information we feel may be of interest to you. If you wish to opt out of certain communications, such as email offers and newsletters, you may do so by clicking the “unsubscribe” link included in the email, and we will make reasonable efforts to discontinue these email communications as soon as practicable.

### III. Disclosure of Information to Third Parties

#### Affiliates and Non-Affiliates

Except as specifically set forth in this Policy, we do not share your personal information with any non-affiliated third party without your permission. We may disclose aggregate information, such as demographic information, and our statistical analyses to third parties, including advertisers or other business partners. This aggregate information does not include your personal information. We may, however, share your personal information with certain entities that control us, are controlled by us, or are under common control with us (our "Affiliates"), so that they and we can offer you products and services that may be of interest to you. We require that our Affiliates agree to process such information based on our instructions and in compliance with this Policy.

#### Service Providers

We may share your personal information with outside companies that perform services for us. When we work with an outside party, we require that these parties agree to process your personal information based on our instructions and in compliance with this Policy. We will take appropriate steps designed to ensure your information will be used solely to provide the services requested by us, and not for other purposes.

We sometimes offer promotions (like sweepstakes) in conjunction with a third party sponsor. If you choose to participate in one of those promotions, we may share your information with the sponsor. We recommend that you review the sponsor’s privacy policy before choosing to participate in a promotion.

#### Business Transactions

We may buy, sell or combine with other businesses. If so, personal and non-personal information that we or other businesses have collected may be transferred as part of the transaction.

#### Third Party Advertisers

We use third-party advertising companies to deliver specific advertisements to you, which appear on pages throughout our Websites. These companies collect non-personal information about your visits to our Websites and other websites in order to provide advertisements about products and services that may be of interest to you. These companies may also aggregate your non-personal information for use in targeted advertising, marketing research, and other similar purposes. Third-party cookies and similar technologies are covered by the third parties’ privacy policies.

#### Other Disclosures

We may disclose your personal information in response to subpoenas, court orders, or other lawful requests by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements. We may also disclose personal information in order to enforce or apply our rights and agreements, or when we believe in good faith that disclosing this information is necessary or advisable, including, for example, to protect the rights, property, or safety of our businesses, our Websites, our customers, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction. We reserve the right to use or disclose non-personal information in any way we see fit.

### IV. Security of the Information We Collect

The security of your personal information is important to us. We maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to secure the personal information we collect on our Websites.

There is always some risk in transmitting information electronically. As we deem appropriate, we use security measures consistent with industry standards. However, we cannot guarantee the security of our databases, nor can we guarantee that information you supply won't be intercepted while being transmitted to us over the Internet.

Keep in mind that any information you choose to post to our Websites, including on any message board, discussion group, or other public posting area, is available to other users with access to those areas.

### V. Accuracy of the Information We Collect

#### Access and Corrections

You may contact us at any time at [privacy@POOLCORP.com](mailto:privacy@POOLCORP.com) to: (1) see what personal information we have about you, if any, (2) request corrections to or deletions of any personal information we have about you, or (3) express any concerns you have about our use of your personal information. However, it is not technologically feasible to remove each and every instance of information we hold on you from our systems, and data may remain in a non-erasable or aggregate form. We may also retain data for a period in our backup or temporary systems, or for longer periods as required by law, contract, or auditing requirements.

### VI. Changes

We reserve the right to change this Policy at any time, and will post any changes to this Policy as soon as they go into effect. Please refer back to this Policy on a regular basis. This Policy was last updated February 22, 2018.
